<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pizza Gromo</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="here_will_be_your_pass">here will be your password...\n Just press GENERATE</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="generate">generate</string>
    <string name="settings_text">settings</string>
    <string name="text_about">Create strong passwords with keywords from your favorite movie to protect your accounts.</string>
    <string name="music">music</string>
    <string name="text_activity_good">Pizza is a dish of Italian origin consisting of a usually round, flat base of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomatoes, cheese, and often various other ingredients (such as various types of sausage, anchovies, mushrooms, onions, olives, vegetables, meat, ham, etc.), which is then baked at a high temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven.[1] A small pizza is sometimes called a pizzetta. A person who makes pizza is known as a pizzaiolo. In Italy, pizza served in a restaurant is presented unsliced, and is eaten with the use of a knife and fork.[2][3] In casual settings, however, it is cut into wedges to be eaten while held in the hand.</string>
    <string name="about"><u>about</u></string>
    <string name="vibration">vibration</string>
    <string name="food_name">pizza</string>
    <string name="benefits_all">1. The average slice of pizza contains 12 grams of protein. \n\nProtein is an essential component of good health. Protein is what helps you to gain muscle, and make hair, blood, connective tissue, antibodies, enzymes, and more. Without enough protein in your diet, you’d start getting sick quite often. While everyone’s daily requirement for protein differs based on their body type and activity levels, it’s important to make sure that you are getting enough. One delicious way to do this is through pizza! The average slice contains 12 grams, which is a great way to get the protein you need while enjoying a delicious meal.\n\n2. Pizza can help you absorb the antioxidant Lycopene.\nLycopene is found in tomatoes, which are used to make the base sauce for pizzas. Lycopene helps to lower blood pressure and bring down high cholesterol. It’s also more easily absorbed from cooked tomatoes as opposed to fresh tomatoes. The next time you’re trying to think of a healthy meal to get for dinner, think pizza!\n3. Fresh veggies are one of the healthiest toppings!\n\nYou probably heard your parents tell you many times to eat your veggies. In fact, you may have even had one of the infamous dinner-table showdowns where you had to stay at the table until you cleaned your plate. We hope that you childhood experiences with vegetables didn’t ruin them for you. Vegetables are still a great part of a healthy diet, which is why at Steel City Pizza in North Charleston, we are proud to offer a wide selection of fresh veggies to use for your pizza toppings. </string>
    <string name="disadnavtages">Like frozen pizzas, pizzeria-made pizza can vary in ingredients and preparation methods.\n\b
Though the nutrition content of pizzeria pizza is not always listed, some pizzeria chains do make nutrition information available to consumers.
\n
Freshly made pizzas often contain healthier ingredients than the more processed ones sold in convenience stores and fast-food restaurants.
\n
Most pizzerias make their dough from scratch using simple ingredients like olive oil and wheat flour.
\n\n
Depending on the restaurant, some use homemade sauces with no added sugar, fresh cheeses and other healthy toppings.
\n
However, no matter if you choose frozen or fresh pizza, piling on extra toppings can make it unhealthy, so be mindful with your selection when eating out.</string>
    <string name="food_region">Authentic Neapolitan pizza (pizza napoletana) is made with San Marzano tomatoes, grown on the volcanic plains south of Mount Vesuvius, and either mozzarella di bufala Campana, made with milk from water buffalo raised in the marshlands of Campania and Lazio[46] or Fior-di-latte. Buffalo mozzarella is protected with its own European protected designation of origin.\n\n[46] Other traditional pizzas include pizza alla marinara, which is topped with marinara sauce and is supposedly the most ancient tomato-topped pizza,[47] pizza capricciosa, which is prepared with mozzarella cheese, baked ham, mushroom, artichoke, and tomato,[48] and pizza pugliese, prepared with tomato, mozzarella, and onions.[49] A popular variant of pizza in Italy is Sicilian pizza (locally called sfincione or sfinciuni),[50][51] a thick-crust or deep-dish pizza originating during the 17th century in Sicily: it is essentially a focaccia that is typically topped with tomato sauce and other ingredients. \n\nUntil the 1860s, sfincione was the type of pizza usually consumed in Sicily, especially in the Western portion of the island.[52] Other variations of pizzas are also found in other regions of Italy, for example pizza al padellino or pizza al tegamino, a small-sized, thick-crust, deep-dish pizza typically served in Turin, Piedmont.</string>
    <string name="food_cultivation">The bottom of the pizza, called the crust, may vary widely according to style – thin as in a typical hand-tossed Neapolitan pizza or thick as in a deep-dish Chicago-style.\n\n It is traditionally plain, but may also be seasoned with garlic or herbs, or stuffed with cheese. The outer edge of the pizza is sometimes referred to as the cornicione.[40] Some pizza dough contains sugar, to help its yeast rise and enhance browning of the crust.[41] \nDipping sauce specifically for pizza was invented by American pizza chain Papa John\'s Pizza in 1984 and has since been adopted by some when eating pizza, especially the crust. Mozzarella cheese is commonly used on pizza, with the buffalo mozzarella produced in the surroundings of Naples.[43] Other cheeses are also used, particularly Italian cheeses including provolone, pecorino romano, ricotta, and scamorza. \n\nLess expensive processed cheeses or cheese analogues have been developed for mass-market pizzas to produce desirable qualities like browning, melting, stretchiness, consistent fat and moisture content, and stable shelf life. This quest to create the ideal and economical pizza cheese has involved many studies and experiments analyzing the impact of vegetable oil, manufacturing and culture processes, denatured whey proteins, and other changes in manufacture.</string>
    <string name="food_history">Foods similar to pizza have been made since the Neolithic Age.[23] Records of people adding other ingredients to bread to make it more flavorful can be found throughout ancient history. In the 6th century BC, the Persian soldiers of the Achaemenid Empire during the rule of Darius the Great baked flatbreads with cheese and dates on top of their battle shields[24][25] and the ancient Greeks supplemented their bread with oils, herbs, and cheese.[26][27] ]n\nAn early reference to a pizza-like food occurs in the Aeneid, when Celaeno, queen of the Harpies, foretells that the Trojans would not find peace until they are forced by hunger to eat their tables (Book III). In Book VII, Aeneas and his men are served a meal that includes round cakes (like pita bread) topped with cooked vegetables. \n\nWhen they eat the bread, they realize that these are the tables prophesied by Celaeno.[28] The first mention of the word pizza comes from a notarial document written in Latin and dating to May 997 AD from Gaeta, demanding a payment of twelve pizzas, a pork shoulder, and a pork kidney on Christmas Day, and 12 pizzas and a couple of chickens on Easter Day.[29] Modern pizza evolved from similar flatbread dishes in Naples, Italy, in the 18th or early 19th century.[30] Before that time, flatbread was often topped with ingredients such as garlic, salt, lard, and cheese. \n\nIt is uncertain when tomatoes were first added and there are many conflicting claims.[30] Until about 1830, pizza was sold from open-air stands and out of pizza bakeries.</string>

    <string-array name="servings">
        <item>Cheese</item>
        <item>Pineapple</item>
        <item>Meat</item>
        <item>Seafood</item>
        <item>Margarita</item>
        <item>Carbonara</item>
        <item>Diablo</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>