<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Caborogo</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="here_will_be_your_pass">here will be your password...\n Just press GENERATE</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="generate">generate</string>
    <string name="settings_text">settings</string>
    <string name="text_about">Create strong passwords with keywords from your favorite movie to protect your accounts.</string>
    <string name="music">music</string>
    <string name="text_activity_good">Cabbage has been selectively bred for head weight and morphological characteristics, frost hardiness, fast growth and storage ability. The appearance of the cabbage head has been given importance in selective breeding, with varieties being chosen for shape, color, firmness and other physical characteristics.[21] Breeding objectives are now focused on increasing resistance to various insects and diseases and improving the nutritional content of cabbage.[22] Scientific research into the genetic modification of B. oleracea crops, including cabbage, has included European Union and United States explorations of greater insect and herbicide resistance.</string>
    <string name="about"><u>about</u></string>
    <string name="vibration">vibration</string>
    <string name="food_name">cabbage</string>
    <string name="benefits_all">Half a cup of cooked cabbage has about a third the vitamin C you need for the day. It also gives you doses of fiber, folate, potassium, magnesium, vitamins A and K, and more. Just leave it in its own juices until bacteria start to feed on it. Sound gross? You’ve probably already eaten it. It’s called sauerkraut. For a spicier, more exotic version, try kimchi, a dish made popular in Korea. When cabbage ferments, it makes natural probiotics that nourish the bacteria in your gut. Those bacteria help your body fight germs, take in nutrients, digest food, and control anxiety. Although you get different nutrients if you cook or ferment it, raw red cabbage in particular might give you the best nutritional boost per serving. Slice it very thinly and leave it for about 10 minutes to help bring out the fullest, most complex flavors. Then add it to salads or sandwiches or turn it into coleslaw. \n\n Although you get different nutrients if you cook or ferment it, raw red cabbage in particular might give you the best nutritional boost per serving. Slice it very thinly and leave it for about 10 minutes to help bring out the fullest, most complex flavors. Then add it to salads or sandwiches or turn it into coleslaw.</string>
    <string name="disadnavtages">Excessive consumption of cabbage may lead to increased intestinal gas which causes bloating and flatulence due to the trisaccharide raffinose, which the human small intestine cannot digest, but is digested by bacteria in the large intestine.[87] \n Cabbage has been linked to outbreaks of some food-borne illnesses, including Listeria monocytogenes[88] and Clostridium botulinum. The latter toxin has been traced to pre-made, packaged coleslaw mixes, while the spores were found on whole cabbages that were otherwise acceptable in appearance.[89] Shigella species are able to survive in shredded cabbage.[89] Two outbreaks of E. coli in the United States have been linked to cabbage consumption. Biological risk assessments have concluded that there is the potential for further outbreaks linked to uncooked cabbage, due to contamination at many stages of the growing, harvesting and packaging processes. Contaminants from water, humans, animals and soil have the potential to be transferred to cabbage, and from there to the end consumer.[90] ]n Whilst not a toxic vegetable, an increase in intestinal gas can lead to the death of many small animals due like rabbits due to Gastrointestinal Stasis.</string>

    <string-array name="servings">
        <item>1 Servings</item>
        <item>2 Servings</item>
        <item>3 Servings</item>
        <item>4 Servings</item>
        <item>5 Servings</item>
        <item>6 Servings</item>
        <item>7 Servings</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>